embeddings에 대해서 배우는
다른 방법을 보도록 합니다.
Let's look at one way to
learn those embeddings.
그것은 Word2Vec라고 합니다.
It's called Word2Vec.
Word2Vec는 매우 잘 수행하는
놀랄만하고 단순한 모델입니다.
Word2Vec is a surprisingly simple
model that works very well.
다음에서 보여지는 것 같이 문장에서
단어들을 가지고 있다고 합시다.
Imagine you had a corpus of
text with a sentence say,
빠른 갈색 여우는 게으른
개를 뛰어넘는다.
the quick brown fox
jumps over the lazy dog.
이 문장에서의 각각의 단어는
우리는 embedding으로 맵핑할 수 있을 것입니다.
For each word in this sentence,
we're going to map it to an embedding.
초기에는 램덤하게.
Initially a random one.
그리고, 단어의 상황을 예측하고
시도할 수 할 수 있도록
And then we're going to use
that embedding to try and
embedding을 사용할 수 있습니다.
predict the context of the word.
이 모델에서, 상황이란 것은 단순하게
근접한 단어들입니다.
In this model, the context is
simply the words that are nearby.
원래 단어 주위에 windows에서
랜덤하게 단어를 선택보세요.
Pick a random word in a window
around the original word
그리고 그것은 당신의 목표입니다.
and that's your target.
지도학습 문제와 같이 정확히
모델을 학습해 보세요.
Then train your model exactly as
if it were a supervised problem.
근접한 단어을 예측하는 모델은
The model you're going to use
to predict this nearby word
단순히 로지스틱 회귀입니다.
is a simple logistic regression.
deep과는 상관없는,
단순한 선형 모델입니다.
Nothing deep about it,
just a simple linear model.